(Dr Koothrappali:)We heard there was a tornado
in Kansas City.
(Dr Koothrappali:)Is that close to you?
(Leonard:)No.
(Mrs Koothrappali:)Where is your brother?
(Priya:)Out with friends.
(Dr Koothrappali:)I don't like it, a young girl
alone in an apartment.
(Mrs Koothrappali:)I'll sleep so much better when
you move back here next month.
(Leonard:)You're moving
back to India?!
(Dr Koothrappali:)Who's that?
(Mrs Koothrappali:)Oh, my God! There's someone
in your apartment.
(Mrs Koothrappali:)Call the police in America!
When were you going
to tell me about this?
(Priya:)Oh, hello, Leonard.
(Priya:)What a pleasant surprise!
(Priya:)Mummy, Daddy, you remember
Rajesh's friend Leonard.
(Dr Koothrappali:)I thought you said Rajesh
was out with his friends.
(Priya:)He has many friends.
(Dr Koothrappali:)Rajesh has many friends?
(Mrs Koothrappali:)Why are you lying to us?
(Leonard:)She's lying because she doesn't
want you to know we're dating.
(Priya:)Leonard!
(Leonard:)Well, what difference
does it make? If you're
(Leonard:)moving back to India,
we're obviously breaking up.
(Priya:)You know what?
(Priya:)I don't want to deal
with this right now.
(Leonard:)So...